=Remnants of Gold=
(Adapted from Gu Long's
"Flying Eagle over the Great Land")
(The main characters
in this drama are fictional)
=Episode 8=
You poisoned an entire street,
but it has no effect
on me.
It worked.
Your men ended up killing each other.
I still have two helpers.
Where are the guardians of the gold?
I can take you straight
to the 300,000 taels of gold.
You know where the gold is?
Of course.
Where?
Hey.
Ghost Couple,
you want the 300,000
taels of gold, too, right?
We do.
You wretched woman.
Either
Ghost Couple
kills me,
or
I kill them.
Is that so?
How did you find out
where the gold was hidden?
That's a bit too easy.
It wasn't easy for you,
but it was very easy for me.
Why else did you invite me back?
How can I trust you?
What you said
at Heisong Post made sense.
The 27 members of my family
can't come back to life.
We might as well
make a fortune together.
However, if revenge isn't taken,
my anger won't subside.
Either you die, or they die.
I will take half
of the 300,000 taels of gold.
That's too much.
I still don't trust you.
Once greed takes hold of your heart,
you will believe it.
I've wanted to kill you for a long time.
You dare to kill us?
Why wouldn't I dare?
Universal Antidote.
Fang.
I'm pouring it.
Why?
You still have residual poison in you.
Close your eyes.
Don't move.
I'll go find Luyao.
Hey,
I let you fight,
and you even hit me?
You were just a feed keeper before.
I am a Battalion Commander.
Over these 30 years,
you've grown far too bold,
even daring to raise a son.
Without my son,
I wouldn't want to live anyway.
I'm sick of living like this.
What are you afraid of?
Move aside.
They are in a hurry to find the gold.
Just let them look for it.
If they find it, kill them.
If they don't, we drink.
What if the Liangzhou Deputy
Military Commissioner escapes
and brings men back?
You and Seventeen leave today.
Abandon the Lieyang Well
camel-horse market.
Where is Seventeen?
Fang?
Hou.
You're not dead yet.
I'm so glad.
Dear!
Wretched woman,
wait for me.
It'll be done soon.
Now, there's only one of you,
but there are two of us.
Two?
Just like we agreed,
I have killed them.
So, let's make a fortune together.
For three hundred thousand taels,
half for you,
and half for me.
You are pitiful.
Wait for me.
Who is this kid?
We've met.
Last time, you went mad,
so I splashed a bucket of water on you.
Where's the spear?
It's on the horse outside.
You can't lose the spear.
Go fetch two horses.
Deputy.
Deputy!
There's a bunch
of bandits on the street.
Miss Zhang and Pingping
are still outside.
Who's Pingping?
Pingping...
Do you want to live and get rich,
or do you want to die?
Go die.
Can we just talk properly?
Sure.
Miss Zhang,
have you made up your mind?
You're the top official of Liangzhou,
yet you colluded with Tie Futu
to poison Zhang Luyao's family to death.
You villain.
Don't you feel any guilt?
Deputy,
what is he talking about?
Hey,
you're one of his men?
Go fetch two horses.
Hou,
what's going on?
Father.
Now, you can call me Father.
Deputy,
tell me.
What is it?
Where are the 300,000 taels
of gold hidden?
You shouldn't ask him.
You should ask me.
Do you have a son?
Guardians of the gold
only have brothers,
no sons.
You have a son?
Yes.
Let me ask you.
Your blade
cuts through iron like butter,
but my soft armor is indestructible.
Killing you two would be child's play!
We both know what the situation is now.
Cut the nonsense.
The outside is full of my men.
If Tie Futu comes in,
he won't be as polite as I am.
To be honest,
your son's throat
wouldn't be nicked.
I'm telling you the truth
about where the gold is hidden.
Ask you?
If you ask,
I'll tell you.
He is his son,
so I'm asking him.
Hou,
what's going on?
Where is the gold?
She won't survive.
What do you need gold for?
Isn't being alive good enough?
With gold,
life will be even better.
Battalion Commander,
30 years ago,
our master buried the gold
and said he would return in a season.
The brothers
guarded it day after day,
guarding it until now.
The older we get,
the more panicked we feel.
Why?
Hou, what's going on?
Our master passed away long ago!
Tell me where the gold is. Where is it?
Battalion Commander,
you won't kill me, will you?
I can end you with a flick of my hand.
Hou,
what are you doing?
Keep heading west.
Once you pass Shiquan Fort,
travel for three more days.
The gold is right in...
Wusu Sea.
Wusu Sea is so vast.
Where exactly is it?
Let Seventeen go.
My son and I will take you there.
Tell your father to prepare the horses.
Father,
go fetch the horses.
Fang,
are you still obedient?
I am.
Bring your spear.
Luyao,
I saw him again.
Just now,
right up there.
Luyao,
forget about revenge.
Good people
should live long lives.
Luyao...
Run...
Run as far away as you can.
There's nowhere left to run.
My father and brothers
must be avenged.
She's dead as a doornail.
You said it yourself
that the dead don't come back to life.
We might as well
make a fortune together!
Tell me.
Where is the gold?
Shaanxi Branch
Regional Military Commission.
When the gold was buried 30 years ago,
there was no Commander-in-Chief yet.
You dare play me?
You killed over a dozen of my men,
and you still dare to lie to my face?
You're scared.
Even bad guys fear the General?
So you don't dare?
I'm going to kill you.
You killed my father and
brothers and lured me back,
all just to find out
where the gold is, no?
Now that you know,
you can kill me now.
Move.
Do you really think
I wouldn't dare kill you?
If you want to die,
I'll send you on your way!
What's so special about
the Regional Military Commission Yamen?
There's nowhere under the sun
I wouldn't dare go!
You darned woman,
what are you trying to do?
Forget it.
I'll send you on your way.
Hurry!
Protect the Officer.
You didn't leave?
I knew you wouldn't leave.
You're asking for death.
I'll kill you guys all the same.
Don't let the jerk get away.
- Yes!
Officer Pu.
How dare you kill
an Embroidered Uniform Guard officer?
Go.
Protect the Officer.
Form up!
How dare you, Futu!
Have you lost your mind?
I'm going to kill every last one of you.
Kill the jerk!
Did you hear that?
Officer Pu said to kill Tie Futu!
Guys, charge!
- Kill him!
Kill.
Protect the Officer.
Father.
I haven't let you leave yet.
Fang,
stop him.
Lad,
don't seek death.
This has nothing to do with you.
Bana,
do you still want your son?
Thank you, Battalion Commander,
for considering my son.
Otherwise, the golden bow
would have been drawn long ago.
Battalion Commander,
you may tolerate me for a moment,
but our men won't tolerate me forever.
I want nothing else now.
I just want to be with my son,
taking it one day at a time.
You're asking for death.
I'll show you the power
of divine machinery.
Officer Pu.
Hurry, bring the divine machinery.
Attack.
Good.
Don't let the jerk escape!
Attack.
Get him.
Officer Pu.
Attack! Get him!
Mount up!
Don't let him get away.
Hurry.
Hurry up.
- Over there!
- Officer Pu.
Officer Pu.
You...
Are you missing your shots on purpose?
Mount up, hurry.
Officer Pu.
Cut him off up ahead.
Deputy Yu.
Follow me.
Let's go.
You two, keep up with Deputy Yu.
Keep up.
Faster.
Deputy Yu is up ahead. Keep up.
Where is my horse?
Gone?
You darn coroner.
What a traitorous scum.
You are all finished.
You're here, too?
Leaving so soon?
Yes.
Where are you heading?
Those people took my guy.
So you want to
go after them to save him?
Go after them
to kill him.
Zhang Luyao is still over there.
How is she?
The whole street is
littered with bodies.
We can't just leave
her alone at Lieyang Well.
(Meet first at Shaquan Inn in Ganzhou,
upper room, with gold.)
Deputy Yu,
have a bite.
Give him some, too.
Eat something.
Does my son have food?
Your son has a spear with him,
the fastest spear in Gansu.
As long as I let you see the gold,
can my son and I
finally leave?
Yes.
Can you untie
the rope on my feet?
Sure.
They'll be untied
once we see the 300,000 taels of gold.
To retrieve the gold,
these men of yours aren't enough.
Who would dare
cross the military guards?
Back then,
when 300,000 taels of gold
were hauled to Wusu Sea,
there were eighteen of us,
and we used a hundred camels.
We didn't care
about the Ming military guards at all.
They didn't even care about me.
Didn't care?
Not one bit.
You don't care about your own life?
I only care about my son's life.
What's your name?
Don't ask.
I don't want to know
yours, either.
I don't have a name.
Bana calls me Seventeen.
Bana is my father.
Don't move.
Don't move a muscle.
My spear is very fast.
Move again,
and it'll pierce
right through your heart.
Why?
We don't even know each other.
It's Deputy Yu's order.
It's better that we
don't know each other.
It makes my spear even faster.
You bury Pingping here?
May she rest in peace.
Once someone's gone,
it's all the same wherever they are.
In the future,
how are we going to tell her family?
I am Pingping's family.
Besides, what "future"?
Only if we stay alive
will there be a "future".
As long as I'm around,
you will have a future.
If you had arrived
a little later in the day,
I wouldn't have
to suffer like this anymore.
Look how nice it is for Pingping.
All her troubles are gone.
You should've said so earlier.
I didn't want to go through
all this trouble either.
Coming back this time,
if it weren't for you...
You wouldn't know what to do, right?
You've said that already.
What is Bancha burning?
He wants to bury those jerks.
He wouldn't burn all of them, right?
(Preview of the Next Episode)
Your guy was captured,
yet you're rushing over to kill him?
He wants to take Liangzhou Deputy
to the Right Chancellor's gold.
He's gone!
He left.
Who's gone?
Which of you
is the Qin Demon of Mount Pingfeng?
=Remnants of Gold=